I'm a deck builder do about three mil. I think the biggest thing that's stopping us is the offer is a little too much
Too much is in what it's kind of slimy
So for instance, I spend quite a bit on an ad spend
I'd rather spend that in your deck make your backyard look like my billboard and you be my radio ad my spokesperson
That kind of thing. So I'll cut the bill down quite a bit when I did it. It worked
Well, my guys are getting feedback that it's just not a good fit. You have any recordings? No. Yeah, that's it
I guarantee if you heard them say you'd be like god, dude
No, you're just like that's like if you had the offer that already worked really well
They're just phrasing it wrong or they're presenting it wrong. They're sucking ass at it. That's all it is. Like
You need to get sales recordings as soon as you listen to you'll hear in two seconds